<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Playstation on </title>
    <link>/tags/playstation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Playstation on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright 2017-2018, all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 22:12:04 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/playstation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cut the Cord Part Deux</title>
      <link>/post/cut-the-cord-part-deux/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 22:12:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/cut-the-cord-part-deux/</guid>
      <description>This is a small addendum to the my original Cutting the cord article. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t read that article pop over there than come on back here. Okay now that we are caught up below are the quick vital links / stats for Sling:
 Sling TV Plans:  Orange - $20/mo (Stream to one device at a time) Blue - $25/mo (Stream to three devices simultaneously) Orange + Blue - $35/mo (Stream to four devices simultaneously)  Channel Lineup Supported Devices  A question that people keep asking me about my original article is how they can get Hallmark and Hallmark Movies &amp;amp; Mysteries channels if they cut the cord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cutting The Cord</title>
      <link>/post/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 00:35:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/first-post/</guid>
      <description>A good friend of mine, Jim, asked me to put this article together some time ago. I finally have what I need in place to make that happen. Cutting the cord is such a buzz wordy phrase these days. This relatively simple task seems to be surrounded by confusion and sometimes misinformation. In simplest terms cutting the cord means using other internet-based services or means to watch live television. Now that we understand what cutting the cord means, let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at three services that can provide you internet-based TV.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>