<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>shickmo.io</title>
    <link>https://shickmo.github.io/hugo-site/</link>
    <description>Recent content on shickmo.io</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://shickmo.github.io/hugo-site/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cutting The Cord</title>
      <link>https://shickmo.github.io/hugo-site/post/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 00:35:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shickmo.github.io/hugo-site/post/first-post/</guid>
      <description>A good friend of mine, Jim, asked me to put this article together some time ago. I finally have what I need in place to make that happen. Cutting the cord is such a buzz wordy phrase these days. This relatively simple task seems to be surrounded by confusion and sometimes misinformation. In simplest terms cutting the cord means using other internet-based services or means to watch live television. Now that we understand what cutting thecord means, let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at three services that can provide you internet-based TV.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://shickmo.github.io/hugo-site/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shickmo.github.io/hugo-site/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my Sanctum Sanctorum Who am I? My name is Ray but I also go by Shickmo. I am beginning a youtube channel, which you can check out by clicking the link below, and this website / blog. This site and youtube channel will focus on technology, Linux (and everything that comes with it, and all things open source. So if you like anything even remotely in the realm of those topics and like to hear about cool open source projects and enjoy learning new things than I have a feeling you might just want to stick around.</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
